(忆往昔)
我想爸爸想要我们继承他的遗志
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off
救助他人 猎杀恶魔
saving people,hunting things...
家族事业
the family business.
爸爸
Dad?
迪恩
Dean!
不是在做梦
It's not a dream.
你听说过灵魂出窍这回事吗？
You ever heard of an out of body experience?
我们是鬼魂…
It means that we're spirits...
人们濒死时出窍的灵魂
of people close to death.
你的儿子快死了 你还在担心柯尔特？
Your son is dying and you're worried about the Colt?
向我的心脏开枪 儿子
You shoot me in the heart, son.
你是不是把那个魔鬼引来了？
You're planning on bringing the demon.
愚蠢地想要和他一决高下？
Having some stupid, macho showdown.
如果你当时就杀了那个魔鬼
If you killed that damn thing,
这一切就不会发生了
none of this would have happened.
我想做个交易
I wanna make a deal.
你比上一个死神漂亮多了
You're prettier than the last reaper.
我会给你柯尔特和子弹 但你得帮助迪恩
I will give you the Colt and the bullet, but you gotta help Dean.
成交了吗？
So we have a deal?
你还得付出更多
You still need to sweeten the pot.
今天是你的幸运日 小子
Today's your lucky day, kid.
你来看着萨姆 行吗？
You watch out for Sammy, okay?
好的
Okay.
爸爸？
Dad?
死亡时间 上午10:41
Time of death, 10:41 a.m.
(现在)
(梅德福   威斯康星州)
国王的火
King of fire.
我讨厌小丑 总是让我毛骨悚然
God, I hate clowns.They always creep me out.
嘘 她喜欢
Shh. She likes them.
最后一次了 诺拉
Last ride, Nora.
快看 妈妈 又一个小丑
Look, Mom, another clown.
你想干什么 吓唬你爸爸吗？
What are you trying to do, scare your father?
亲爱的
Hey.
快看 妈妈 小丑
Look, Mom, the clown.
你错过了
You missed him.
[邪恶力量 第2季第2集]
他之前…
Before he
和你说过什么吗？
Did he say anything to you?
任何事？
About anything?
没有
No.
什么也没说
Nothing.
(一周后)
车修的怎样了？
How this car coming along?
早着呢
Slow.
是吗？
Yeah?
需要帮忙吗？
Need any help?
什么？是你在车底吗？
What, you under a hood?
不用了
I'll pass.
其他的呢？
Need anything else, then?
别说了 萨姆
Stop it, Sam.
说什么？
Stop what?
别再问我是否需要什么
Stop asking if I need anything.
别再问我有事没事 我很好
Stop asking if I'm okay. I'm okay.
真的 我保证
Really. I promise.
好吧 迪恩 只是…
All right. Dean, it's just
我们已经在鲍比这呆了一周了
We've been at Bobby's for a week and
你也一次都没提过爸爸的事
you haven't brought up Dad once.
你知道吗？你说对了
You know what? You're right.
靠近点
Come here.
这样我可以把头靠在你的肩膀上
I'm wanna lay my head gently on your shoulder.
也许我们可以抱着痛哭一场
Maybe we can cry, hug.
- 也许再来段慢舞 - 别敷衍我了 迪恩
- Maybe even slow dance. - Don't patronize me, Dean.
爸爸死了柯尔特枪也不见了 很明显地
Dad is dead.The Colt is gone and it seems pretty damn likely
是那个魔鬼在搞鬼 但你却当什么事都没发生过
the demon is behind all this, and you're acting like nothing's happened
- 为什么说？- 随便说些什么 可以吗？
- Why saySay something, all right?
说点什么吧 难道你不愤怒？不想报仇吗？
Hell, say anything. Aren't you angry? Don't you want revenge?
可你现在只知道蹲在这里修这辆烂车
But all you do it You sit out here all day long, buried underneath this car.
- 报仇？- 是啊 - 听起来不错
- Revenge, huh? - Yeah. - Sounds good.
知道那魔鬼在哪吗？
Got any leads on where the demon is?
弄懂老爸的那些研究了吗？我是没有啦
You making heads or tails of Dad's research? I sure aingt.
就算我找到了它…
But you know, when we do finally find it
哦
oh
不 等等 你说了 柯尔特不见了
No, wait. Like you said, the Colt's gone.
但我猜你肯定会找到其他方法的
I'm sure you've figured out a way to kill it.
我们什么都没有 萨姆 什么都没
We got nothing, Sam. Nothing, okay?
我唯一能做的就是修车
See, the only thing I can do, is I can work on the car.
我们不是什么都没有
Well, we got something, all right?
这就是我来找你的原因
That's what I came to tell you.
这是爸爸其中一个旧手机
It's one of Dad's old phones.
我花了很长时间才解开语音信箱的密码 听听这
Took me a while, but I cracked his voice mail.Listen to this.
约翰 我是埃伦… 又是我
John, it's Ellen. Again.
别固执了 你知道我帮的到你 回我电话
Look, don't be stubborn. You know I can help you. Call me.
那条信息是4个月前的
That message is four months old.
老爸把那个女人的信息保留了4个月？
Dad saved that for four months?
- 是的 - 埃伦是谁？
- Yeah - Who's Ellen?
- 老爸的日记里有提到吗？- 没有
- Any mention of her in Dad's journal? - No.
但是我查了下电话号码 找到了地址
But I ran a trace on the phone number and I got an address.
问问鲍比 我们是不是可以用一下他的车
Ask Bobby if we can use one of his cars.
这真是羞辱
This is humiliating.
我感觉像是可怜的家庭主妇
I feel like a frigging soccer mom.
这是鲍比那唯一一辆可以开的车了
It's the only car Bobby had running.
有人吗？
Hello?
- 有人吗？- 好吧
- Anybody here? - Hey.
- 嘿 你有带… - 当然带了
- Did you bring the... ? - Of course.
嘿 伙计？
Hey, buddy.
- 我猜他一定不是埃伦了 - 是啊
- I'm guessing that isn't Ellen. - Yeah.
哦 天哪 别告诉我那是来福枪
Oh, God, please let that be a rifle.
不 我真的很高兴能见到你
No. I'm just real happy to see you.
- 别动 - 不动 我知道了
- Don't move. - Not moving. Copy that.
你该知道 小姐
You should know something, Miss
当你用来福枪顶着人时
When you put a rifle on someone,
你最好不要顶着他们的背
you won't put it right against their back...
因为那样很容易就会…
because it makes it real easy to do
这样
That!
萨姆
Sam!
我需要点帮助
I need some help in here.
我看不见了 看不见了
Can't see. I can't even see.
对不起 迪恩
Sorry, Dean.
我现在不行 我…
I can't right now. I'm, uh,
被抓了
a little tied up.
萨姆 迪恩
Sam? Dean?
温彻斯特家的？
Winchester?
是的
Yeah.
该死的
Son of a bitch.
妈 你认识他们？
Mom, you know these guys?
是的 我想他们是约翰·温彻斯特的儿子
Yeah, I think these are John Winchester's boys.
嘿 我叫埃伦
Hey, I'm Ellen.
那是我的女儿 乔
My daughter, Jo.
嘿
Hey.
你不会再打我了吧？
You're not gonna hit me again, are you?
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
你打过电话给我们的爸爸 说你可以帮忙
You called our dad, said you could help.
帮什么忙？
Help with what?
嗯
Well,
当然是那个魔鬼
the demon, of course.
我听说他找到它了
I heard he was closing in on it.
难道我在《猎魔周刊》漏看什么了吗？
Was there an article in Demon Hunters Quarterly that I missed?
- 我是说你是谁？- 你是怎么知道这些事的？
- Who are you? - How do you know this?
嘿 我只是开酒吧的
Hey, I just run a saloon.
但是猎手们也经常路过这里
But hunters have been known to pass through now and again.
你爸爸很久前也来过
Including your dad a long time ago.
- 约翰那时就像家人一样 - 哦 是的？
- John was like family once. - Oh, yeah?
我是说他从没提起过你
How come he's never mentioned you before?
那你得问他啊
You'd have to ask him that.
那么 我们能帮你们什么忙？
So why exactly do we need your help?
嘿 不用勉强
Hey, don't do me any favors.
你瞧 如果不需要帮忙可以
Look, if you don't want my help, fine.
要离开的话，你走的时候干脆点
Don't let the door smack your ass on the way out.
但是约翰一般不会让你们来的 除非…
But John wouldn't have sent you if
不是他叫你们来的
He didn't send you.
他还好吗？
He's all right, isn't he?
不好
No.
不 他不好
No, he isn't.
我们觉得是那魔鬼干的
It was the demon, we think.
我想它比他早了一步
It just got him before he got it, I guess.
- 我很抱歉 - 没关系
- I'm so sorry. - It's okay.
我们都很好
We're all right.
是吗？我清楚你们和你们的爸爸的关系…
Really? I know how close you and your dad
真的 女士 我很好
Really,Lady. I'm fine.
你瞧 如果你能帮忙…
So look. If you can help...
我们可以用上一切有用的
we could use all the help we can get.
嗯 我们不行
Well, we can't.
但阿什行
But Ash will.
- 谁是阿什？- 阿什
- Who's Ash? - Ash?
怎么了？
What?
关门了吗？
Closing time?
- 他就是阿什？- 是的
- That's Ash? - Mm - hm.
他是个天才
He's a genius.
开玩笑吧 这家伙是天才
You gotta be kidding. He's no genius.
他就像是Lynyrd Skynyrd乐队里打杂的
He's a Lynyrd Skynyrd roadie.
- 我喜欢你 - 谢谢
- I like you. - Thanks.
就让他试试吧
Just give him a chance.
好吧
All right.
这些我老爸一年的劳动成果 所以…
This stuff's a year's worth of our dad's work.
让我们看看你能懂多少
So let's see what you make of it.
拜托 这些东西不是真的
Come on. This crap aingt real.
没人能用这个来追踪一个魔鬼
There aingt nobody that can track a demon like this.
我们的爸爸可以
Our dad could.
这些是非参数的统计数据
These are nonparametric statistical overviews.
交叉光谱的相互关系 我是说…
Cross - spectrum correlations. I mean...
好家伙
damn.
它们都是预兆
They're signs.
征兆 如果你能追踪它们 就能追踪到那魔鬼
Omens. If you can track them, you can track this demon.
像是庄稼歉收 电子风暴
You know, like crop failures, electrical storms.
你们被雷劈过吗？那可不是好玩的
You ever been struck by lightning?It aingt fun.
- 你能追踪到吗？- 是的 有了这个 我想我能
- Can you track it or not? - Yeah, with this, I think so.
但要花点时间 给我…
But it's gonna take time. Uh, give me...
51小时
51 hours.
- 嘿 伙计 - 嗯？
- Hey, man. - Yeah.
顺便说一下 我喜欢你的发型
By the way, I, uh, dig the haircut.
前面的是为了工作
All business up front...
后面的是为了派对
and party in the back.
嘿 埃伦 那是什么？
Hey, Ellen, what is that?
那是报警器
It's a police scanner.
- 小心点为好 - 不 不 不 不 那个…文件夹
We,uh,keep tabs on things. - No,no,no.The,um,The folder.
我打算把这给一个朋友的 但是…
I was gonna give this to a friend of mine. But...
看看吧
take a look
如果你想做的话
if you want.
谢谢
Thanks.
你母亲是怎么进入这行的？
How'd your mom get into this stuff, anyway?
我的爸爸
My dad.
他是个猎手
He was a hunter.
去世了
He passed away.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
那是很久以前的事了
It's a long time ago.
我那时还是个孩子
I was just a kid.
对你爸爸的事我很遗憾
I'm sorry to hear about your dad.
是啊
Yeah.
那么
So,
我想我有51个小时要消磨了
I guess I got 51 hours to waste.
也许今晚我们能…
Maybe tonight we should...
哦 你知道吗？还是算了
No, you know what? Never mind.
- 什么？- 没什么 只是…
- What? - Nothing, just, uh...
挑错了地点和时间
wrong place, wrong time.
我还以为你会向我挑逗一下呢
you know i thought you were gonna toss me some cheap line.
大多数猎手来这里
Most hunters come through that door
都想从我这得到些好处 像是
think they can get in my pants with some...
皮萨 肌肉 齐柏林飞艇IV的第一张唱片
pizza, a six - pack, and Side 1 of Zeppelin IV.
一群卑鄙的家伙
What a bunch of scumbags.
但你不是
Not you.
我想也是
I guess not.
迪恩 过来下 看看这个
Dean, come here. Check this out.
好的
Yeah.
埃伦找到的 几宗发生在离这不远地方的谋杀案
A few murders, not far from here, that Ellen caught wind of.
看来那儿有东西可以猎杀
Looks to me like there might be a hunt.
- 是的 所以？- 所以
- Yeah, so? - So
我告诉她我们可以去查查
I told her we'd check it out.
你开玩笑吧 小丑杀手？
You gotta be kidding me. A killer clown?
是的 他没有伤害那女孩 却杀了她的父母
He left the daughter unharmed and killed the parents.
正确的说是撕成了碎片
Ripped them to pieces.
这家人去了什么游乐园吗？
This family was at a carnival that night?
是的 库珀游乐园
Right. The Cooper Carnival.
你怎么知道我们要找的
So how do you know we're
不是什么小丑装的变态的戏班演员？
not dealing with some psycho in a clown suit?
警方毫无线索
Well.The cops have no viable leads
而且当时所有的戏班人员都在拆设施…
and all the employees were tearing down shop.
都有不在场证明
Alibis all around.
再说那小女孩说见到那小丑凭空消失了
Plus the girl said she saw a clown vanish into thin air.
警方当然会说是创伤引起的幻觉
Cops are saying trauma, of course.
我知道你在想什么 萨姆
I know what you're thinking, Sam.
“为什么会是小丑？”
Why did it have to be clowns?
哦 饶了我吧
Oh, give me a break.
你以为我不记得了吗？
You didn't think I remembered, did you?
你每次在电视见到麦当劳叔叔 都会哭个不停
You still bust out crying when you see Ronald McDonald on the television.
至少我不会晕机
I'm not afraid of flying.
- 飞机会坠毁的 - 很显然小丑会杀人
- Planes crash. - Apparently, clowns kill.
这样的谋杀案 以前有过吗？
So these types of murders, they ever happen before?
根据记录 1981年…
According to the file, 1981.
邦克兄弟马戏团
The Bunker Brothers Circus.
同样的手法 发生在三个不同的时间和地点
Same m.o. It happened three different times, three different locales.
有点奇怪 如果是怨灵
If it is a spirit, it's usually bound
一般来说 会固定在同一个地点 房子或镇子
to a specific locale you know a house or a town.
怎么会从一个城市到另一个？一个表演会到另一个呢？
How's this one moving from carnival to carnival?
也许是被诅咒的东西
Cursed object, maybe.
怨灵让自己附在某样东西上
The spirit attaches itself to something,
- 跟着马戏团到处走 - 好极了 超常的清道夫
- carnival carries it around with them. - Great. Paranormal scavenger hunt.
这活是你接的
This case was your idea.
话说回来 你是怎么了？巴不得早点接下这活
By the way, why is that?You were awfully quick to jump on this job.
- 那又如何？- 这不像你的作风 就这意思
- So? - It's just not like you, that's all.
我还以为 你只是一心想追杀那魔鬼
I thought you were hell bent for leather on the demon hunt.
我不知道 只是觉得
I don't know. I just think, taking this job,
爸爸在的话 也会希望我们接下这活的
it's what Dad would've wanted us to do.
- 老爸希望的？- 是的
- What Dad would've wanted? - Yeah.
怎么了？
So?
没什么
Nothing.
看看这个
Check it out.
埃文 看哪
Hey, Evan, look.
- 可怕吧 - 是的 爸爸 可怕
- Scary. - Yeah, Dad. Scary.
那里是什么？
What's over here?
我在你这么大的时候 这东西都会把我吓的掉裤子了
Wow.You know, when I was your age, this would've scared the pants off me.
埃文
Evan?
嘿
Hey...
什么？
What is it?
我…
I...
我看到一个小丑
I saw a clown.
别害怕小丑
Don't be afraid of clowns.
他们很友好 是你的朋友
They're nice. They're your friends.
好吗？走吧
Okay? Come on.
爸爸
Dad.
埃文
Evan?
什么事？
What is it?
你说的对
You were right.
他是我的朋友
He is my friend.
看看这个
Check it out.
5点钟的位置
Five.
拿到她的号码了吗？
Did you get her number?
- 又有谋杀案了？- 昨晚又死了两个人
- More murders? - Two more last night.
被撕成了碎片
They were ripped to shreds.
旁边还有一个男孩
And they had a little boy with them.
说是小丑干的
Who fingered a clown.
什么？
What?
是的 一个凭空消失的小丑
Yes, a clown, who vanished into thin air.
迪恩 你知道 找一件被诅咒的物品
Dean, you know, looking for a cursed object, it's like...
就像是大海捞针 任何东西都可能是的
trying to find a needle in a stack of needles. It could be anything.
这时EMF就派上用场了 我们只要扫描每一样东西就行了
It's bound to give off EMFs. We'll just have to scan everything.
哦 好极了 那样做一点都不会引人注意啊
Oh, good. That's nice and inconspicuous.
只要我们混进去就行了
I guess we'll just have to blend in.
对不起
Excuse me.
我们在找库珀先生 你有见过他吗？
We're looking for a Mr. Cooper. Have you seen him?
那是什么意思？玩笑话吗？
What is that, some kind of joke?
- 哦 天哪 抱歉 - 你以为我一点都不想
- Oh, God, I'm sorry. - You think I wouldn't
看到库珀先生或者日落吗？
give my eyeteeth to see Mr. Cooper or a sunset or anything at all?
你不来帮我一把吗？
Wanna give me a little help here?
真的不了
Not really.
嘿 巴里 出什么事了？
Hey, Barry, is there a problem?
- 这家伙讨厌瞎子 - 不 我没有
- Yeah, this guy hates blind people. - No, I don't
- 嘿 伙计 你怎么回事？- 没事 只是有点误会
- What's your problem? - It's just a little misunderstanding.
有点？
"Little"?
- 你这该死的 - 不 不 不
- You son of a bitch. - No, I'm just
有人能告诉我库珀先生在哪吗？
Can somebody tell me where Mr. Cooper is?
求你们了？
Please?
你们加入的真不是时候
You boys picked a hell of a time to join up.
坐吧
Take a seat.
我们正好在这里惹上了一些麻烦
We got all kinds of local trouble.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
一对夫妇被谋杀了 警察总喜欢从这查起
A couple of folks got murdered. Cops always seem to start here first.
你们以前在游乐园做过吗？
So you two ever worked the circuit before?
呃 是的 先生 去年在德克萨斯州和阿肯色州做过
Yes, sir. Last year through Texas and Arkansas.
做什么？
Yeah.Doing what?
驯马师？
Ride jockeys?
飞刀？
Butcher?
- 空中飞人？- 是的 我们是…
- A&S men? Yeah.I...
什么都做的
Little bit of everything.
你们俩从没表演过杂技吧？
You two have never worked a show in your lives before, have you?
没有
Nope.
但我们真的很需要这工作
But we really need the work.
而且萨姆喜欢上了那个有胡子的女士
So And Sam here has got a thing for the bearded lady.
你们看到那照片了吗？
You see that picture?
那是我父亲
That's my daddy.
你和他长的一模一样
You look just like him.
他也是做这行的
He was in the business.
组织一种很恐怖的表演 直到大多数地方都禁止他的表演
Ran a freak show, till they outlawed them most places.
很显然他们觉得 那些被展出的东西都很畸形
Apparently, displaying the deformed isn't dignified.
所以多数的表演者被送进了
So most of the performers went from honest work...
医院和精神病院
to rotting in hospitals and asylums.
那算进步吧
That's progress,
也许吧
I guess.
你们看到了 这地方
You see, this place,
是流浪者的避风港
it's a refuge for outcasts.
一直以来都是
Always has been.
那些不能融入社会的人的收容所
For folks that don't fit in nowhere else.
但是你们两个…
But you two...
应该去上学
you should go to school.
找个女朋友
Find a couple of girls.
生2 3个孩子
Have 2.5 kids.
过正常的生活
Live regular.
先生…
Sir?
我们不想去上学
We don't wanna go to school.
我们也不想过正常的生活
And we don't want regular.
我们想要这工作
We want this.
怎么了？
Huh. What?
那一套“我不想上学”的话
That whole, uh, "I don't wanna go back to school" thing.
你只是…
Were you just
对库珀说的 还是…
saying that to Cooper, or, were you,
你知道的
you know,
只是说说而已？
saying it?
- 我不知道 - 你不知道？
- Sam? - I don't know.You don't know.
我以为只要那魔鬼一死
I thought once the demon was dead and the fat lady sings...
你就会离开 回到那个懦夫大学去
that you were gonna take off, head back to Wussy State.
我改变主意了
I'm having second thoughts.
- 真的吗？- 是的 我想…
- Really? - Yeah, I think.
爸爸会希望我继续做下去的
Dad wanted me to stick with the job.
你什么时候开始听老爸的话？
Since when do you give a damn?
你花了半辈子的时间 都在和他作对啊
You spent your life doing what he didn't want.
从他死后 可以吗？
Since he died.Okay?
有问题吗？
You have a problem with that?
没有 一点问题都没有
No, I don't have a problem at all.
那是什么？
Were you even scared? No.
- 你好？- 嘿
- Hello. Hey, man.
怎么了？听起来你好像看到了小丑
What's the matter? You sound like you just saw a clown.
很好笑
Very funny.
事实上是骨头
Skeleton, actually.
- 真人的骨头？- 就在鬼屋
- Like a real human skeleton? - In the fun house.
听着 我在想 如果那怨灵不是附在被诅咒的东西上
Listen, I was thinking What if the spirit isn't attached to a cursed object?
而是在自己的遗骸上呢
What if it's attached to remains?
- EMF有反应吗？- 没有 但是…
- Did bones give off EMF? - No, but
我们应该去看看 我这就去你那
We should check it out.I'm heading to you.
你在这干什么 孩子？
What are you doing here, kid?
- 扫垃圾 - 废话
- I was just sweeping. - Bull.
你刚才在说什么？骨头？
And what were you talking about? Skeletons?
什么是EMF？
What's EMF?
好家伙 你们盲人的听力真好
Your blind man hearing is out of control.
我们是紧密的团体 不喜欢外来人
We're a tight group. We don't like outsiders.
自己的麻烦自己处理
We take care of our own problems.
- 我们有麻烦吗？- 你告诉我吧 不是你
- We got a problem? - Well, you tell me.
在那说什么人骨的啊
You're the one talking about human bones.
你相信鬼魂吗？
Do you believe in ghosts?
什么？
What?
我弟弟和我…
My brother and me, um...
正在写一本这方面的书
we're writing a book about them.
- 怎么这么久？- 说来话长
- What took you so long? - Long story.
妈咪 快看那个小丑
Mommy, look at the clown.
什么小丑？
What clown?
走吧 宝贝 走吧
Come on, sweetie. Come on.
迪恩 真不敢相信
I cannot believe
你和帕帕说了杀人小丑的事
you told Papazian about the homicidal phantom clown.
我说的是 一个关于隐形杀人小丑的传说
I told him an urban legend about a homicidal phantom clown.
- 我没说那是真的 - 拿低点
- I never said it was real. - Keep that down.
噢 我知道了
Oh, and get this:
我说了81年邦克兄弟马戏团
I mentioned the Bunker Brothers Circus in 81...
和他们邪恶小丑的事 猜猜怎么着
and their, uh, evil clown apocalypse.Guess what?
什么？
What?
在库珀先生拥有库珀游乐园前
Before Mr. Cooper owned Cooper Carnival...
他为邦克兄弟工作过
he worked for Bunker Brothers.
他曾是他们的后勤主管
He was their lot manager.
所以不管那怨灵附在什么东西上
Whatever the spirit's attached to,
- 库珀一直把它带在身边？- 差不多
- Cooper brought it with him? - Something like that.
真不敢相信我们一直在讨论小丑
I can't believe we keep talking about clowns.
想要进来玩吗？
Dean.Wanna come in and play?
想要见见妈咪和爹地吗？他们就在楼上
Wanna see Mommy and Daddy? They're upstairs.
嘿
Hey! Hey!
萨姆 小心了
Sam, watch out!
这出什么事了？
What's going on here?
哦 天哪 你们在对我的女儿做什么
What are you doing to my daughter?
离我的孩子远点
Get out! Get out of my house!
妈咪 爹地 他们开枪打了我的小丑
Mommy, Daddy, they shot my clown.
他们真的看到我们的车牌了吗？
You really think they saw our plates?
我可不想冒险
I don't wanna take the chance.
再说 我讨厌这怪东西
Besides, I hate this freaking thing anyway.
有件事是肯定的
Well, one thing's for sure.
什么？
What's that?
我们对付的不是一个鬼魂
We're not dealing with a spirit.
盐弹打到的是实体
That rock salt hit something solid.
是的 一个人 或是一个可以隐形的生物吗？
Yeah. A person? Or maybe a creature that can make itself invisible?
是的 而且穿成小丑来吸引小孩？
And dresses up like a clown for kicks?
在老爸的日记里有记录吗？
Did it says anything in Dad's journal?
没有
Nope.
你打给谁？
Who you calling?
也许埃伦 或者那个叫阿什的会知道些什么
Maybe Ellen or that guy Ash will know something.
嘿 呃…
Hey, you think, uh ?
你觉得爸爸是不是喜欢过埃伦？
You think Dad and Ellen ever had a thing?
不可能
No way.
那为什么他不告诉我们？
Then why didn't he tell us about her?
不知道 也许他们闹翻了吧
I don't know. Maybe they had some sort of falling out.
是啊
Yeah.
你看到过爸爸和谁闹翻过吗？
You ever notice Dad had a falling out with just about everybody?
别跟我玩深沉
Well, don't get all maudlin on the man.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
我指你那种深沉凝重的表情 我才不吃那套呢
This strong, silent thing of yours. It's crap. I'm over it.
我们说的不是别人 是爸爸啊
This isn't just anyone. This is Dad.
我知道你对他的感受
I know how you felt about the man.
剩剩吧 就因为我不是那样的多愁善感…
Back off, all right? Just because I'm not caring and sharing
不 不是这个 迪恩 我不管你是怎么接受的
No, that's not what this is about.
但你必须接受爸爸的死
I don't care how you deal with this, but you have to deal with it, man.
听着 我是你的兄弟 我只是想确认你真的没事
I'm your brother. I wanna make sure you're okay.
哥们 我没事 我没事
Dude, I'm okay. I'm okay, okay?
如果还有人问我有没有事 我发誓
The next person who asks me if I'm okay,
一定先给他一拳
I'm gonna start throwing punches.
这些是你的事 别冲着我来
These are your issues. Quit dumping them on me.
你在说什么呢？
What?
我对你突然间服从老爸觉得好奇
It's really interesting......this obedience you have to Dad.
像是 “哦 爸爸会要我做什么呢？”
It's like, "Oh, what would Dad want?"
你一生都在和他作对
You spent your life slugging it out with that man.
我是说 上一次你看到他时 还是你挑起争吵的
You picked a fight with him the last time you saw him.
现在他死了 你才想要改正吗？
Now that he's dead you wanna make it right?
对不起了 萨姆 你改不了了 太少也太迟了
Sorry, but you can't. It's too late.
为什么这么说我？
Why are you saying this to me?
我想你好好面对自己 我已经接受老爸的死了
I want you to be honest with yourself.I'm dealing with Dad's death.
你呢？
Are you?
我要给埃伦打电话了
I'm gonna call Ellen.
太感谢了
Thanks a lot.
是罗刹
Rakshasa.
- 什么东西？- 埃伦说最有可能是这个了
- What's that? - Ellen's best guess.
一种古印度怪物 他们能呈现人形
It's a race of ancient Hindu creatures.
以人肉为生
They appear in human form.
可以使自己隐身
They feed on human flesh.
没有别人的邀请 他们进不了房屋
.They cannot enter a home without first being invited.
所以他们穿成小丑 让孩子们请他们进去
So they dress up like clowns and the children invite them in.
- 他们为什么不吃孩子？- 不知道
- Why don't they munch on the kids? - Don't know
肉太少了吧？
Not enough meat, maybe?
- 还有什么？- 罗刹住在很肮脏的地方
- What else you find out? - Apparently, rakshasas live in squalor.
睡在用死昆虫铺成的床上
They sleep on a bed of dead insects.
他们的餐数很少 每20到30年一次
Nice. And they have to feed a few times......every 20 to 30 years.
- 我猜他们的新陈代谢很慢吧 - 说的过去
- Slow metabolism, I guess. - Makes sense.
这年是在游乐园 81年是在邦克兄弟马戏团
I mean, the carnival today, the Bunker Brothers in 81.
也许以前还有
Right. Probably more before that.
萨姆 谁在两个地方都做过事？
Who do we know that worked both shows?
- 库珀 - 库珀
- Cooper - Cooper.
那张他父亲的照片
You know, that picture of his father,
和他一模一样
that looked just like him.
你觉得就是他吗？
You think maybe it was him?
谁知道他几岁了？
Well, who knows how old he is.
埃伦有说怎么杀死他吗？
Ellen say how to kill him?
传说中是用纯铜的匕首
Legend goes, a dagger made of pure brass.
我想我知道去哪可以弄到一把
I think I know where to get one.
在刺穿库珀前 我们得弄清楚是不是他
Before we go stabbing things into Cooper, we wanna make sure it's him.
哦 你真是小心谨慎的家伙 萨姆
Oh, you're such a stickler for detail, Sammy.
好了 我去找武器
All right, I'll round up the blade.
你去查查库珀的睡床
You go check if Cooper's got bedbugs.
我有各种各样的刀子
Well, I got all kinds of knives.
不知道有没有铜的
I don't know if I got a brass one, though.
你在做什么？
What do you think you're doing?
去箱子里看看
Check the trunk.
你？
You?
是我
Me.
好了
Jeez.
天哪
All right!
嘿
Hey.
库珀把我当成了偷窥狂 但他不是
So Cooper thinks I'm a peeping Tom, but it's not him.
是的 所以我过来了
Yeah, so I gathered.
是那个瞎子 他就在这儿什么地方
It's the blind guy. He's here somewhere.
- 你有拿到… - 铜刀吗？没有
- Did you get...? - The brass blades?No.
真是倒霉的日子
No, it's just been one of those days.
我有办法 快来
I got an idea. Come on.
迪恩 找到出路 好吗？
Dean, find the maze, okay?
- 在哪？- 不知道
- Where is it?I don't know.
我们不是应该看得到他的衣服吗？
Shouldn't we see his clothes walking around?
- 迪恩 他在哪？- 我不知道
- Dean, where his he? - I don't know.
萨姆 背后
Sam, behind you! Behind you!
我讨厌鬼屋
I hate fun houses.
小伙子们干得不错嘛
You boys did a hell of a job.
- 你们父亲一定会自豪的 - 谢谢
Your dad would be proud. - Thanks.
哦 是的 我得 呃…
Oh, yeah, um, I've gotta Uh Uh
我得去…
I gotta go...
那儿了…
over there.
现在就去
Right now.
- 那么 - 那么
- So? Ahem... - So?
我还能见到你吗？
Am I gonna see you again?
你想吗？
Do you want to?
我不会讨厌的
I wouldn't hate it.
我能对你说实话吗？
Can I be honest with you?
你瞧 通常
See, normally,
我早就把你迷倒了
I'd be hitting on you so fast it would make your head spin.
但是
But
这些日子…
these days...
我不知道
I don't know.
错误的地点
Wrong place...
错误的时间吗？
wrong time?
没关系 我明白
It's okay, I get it.
你们去哪了？
Where have you guys been?
- 我正等着你们呢 - 我们去干活了 阿什
- Been waiting for you. - We were working a job, Ash.
- 小丑？- 小丑？什么…
- Clowns? - Clowns? What the ?
有事告诉我们吗 阿什？
Got something for us, Ash?
你找到那魔鬼了？
Did you find the demon?
不在附近
It's nowhere around.
至少我没有找到
At least, nowhere I can find.
但是如果这狗娘养的一出现
But if this fugly bastard raises its head, I'll know.
我就会知道 就像鲨鱼闻到血腥一样
I mean, I'm on it like Divine on dog dookie.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
意思是
I mean,
在世界任何地方 只要有类似的征兆或预兆
any of those signs or omens appear anywhere in the world...
我的设备就会让火警一样响起来
my rig will go off.Like a fire alarm.
你介意吗？
Would you mind...?
干什么呢 伙计？
- Yeah. - What's up, man?
阿什 你从哪学到这些的？
Where did you learn to do all this?
麻省理工大学 在我因打架被赶出去前
MIT. Before I got bounced for fighting.
麻省理工大学？
- MIT?
波士顿的一所学校
It's a school in Boston.
好的
Okay.
发现什么就尽快通知我们吧？
Give us a call as soon as you know something?
听你们的
Si. Si, compadre.
嘿 听着
Hey, listen.
如果你们想找个地方住 我这里有地方
If you boys need a place to stay, I got a couple beds.
谢谢 不过不需要
Thanks, but no.
还有些事要做呢
No, there's something I gotta finish.
好吧
Okay.
你是对的
You were right.
关于什么？
About what?
关于我和爸爸
About me and Dad.
抱歉上次和他在一起的时候 我挑起了争吵
I'm sorry that the last time I was with him, I tried to pick a fight.
也能抱歉我一直都在生他的气
I'm sorry that I spent most of my life angry at him.
我知道的就是 到他死时
I mean, for all I know, he died thinking that I hate him.
也觉得我在恨他
So you're right.
所以你说对了
What I'm doing right now,
我现在做的太少了…
it is too little.
太迟了
It's too late.
我很想他
I miss him, man.
觉得内疚极了
And I feel guilty as hell.
而且我没有没事…
And I'm not all right.
一点都没…
Not at all.
但你也是
But neither are you.
我就知道这些
That much I know.
你继续修车吧
I'll let you get back to work.